Guide to the Second Stage Theater Records, 1973 - [ongoing]
Second Stage Theater Records, 1973 - [ongoing]
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.). Second Stage.
2000-41
12.75
25
Second Stage is an organization of students at Wesleyan University dedicated to producing theater and other performances. Founded in 1973, the mostly volunteer student group manages the administration, staging, finances, and selection of approximately thirty-five shows each academic year, usually staged in the '92 Patricelli Theater. Second Stage provides an opportunity for aspiring playwrights, directors, actors, and technicians to stage their very own productions. The Theater Department and Second Stage work closely together, sharing facilities and equipment.
The Second Stage Theater Records include administrative information about the student group, organized by each season and year. Information may include: staff lists; seasonal production lists; correspondence; clippings; financial information; production notes; show applications and responses; posters; and other administrative files. Some seasons have separate files for each production, and some seasons have sparse documentation.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Transferred from Second Stage in 2000; additional materials transferred in 2008. Accession #2010-38 transferred in December 2010 by Jenna Robbins, class of 2013.
Historical Note
Second Stage is an organization of students at Wesleyan University dedicated to producing theater and other performances. Founded in 1973 by Jan Eliasberg (class of 1974) with Samuel Miller (class of 1975), it originated as an alternative to Theater Department productions. In 1973, the Wesleyan Theater Department moved from the '92 Theater building (now known as the '92 Patricelli Theater) into the new Center for the Arts theater. This made it possible for Second Stage to use the '92 Theater space, and they frequently staged noontime performances of theater, music, and poetry. Second Stage soon began to produce full-length shows, with each production running for several days.
The mostly volunteer student group manages the administration, staging, finances, and selection of approximately thirty-five shows each academic year. Second Stage provides an opportunity for aspiring playwrights, directors, actors, and technicians to stage their very own productions. Many, but not all, of the fifteen or so Second Stage staff members are theater majors. A Managing Liaison, a Building/Maintenance Liaison, and a Lighting and Rigging Liaison, the only paid members of Second Stage, serve as links to the Theater Department, which does not have oversight of the group. However, the department and Second Stage work closely together, sharing facilities and equipment. Second Stage is funded by the Wesleyan Student Assembly, and the paid staff members are funded by the Theater Department.
Collection Overview
The Second Stage Theater Records include administrative information about the student group, organized by each season and year. Information may include: staff lists; seasonal production lists; correspondence; clippings; financial information; production notes; show applications and responses; posters; and other administrative files. Some seasons have separate files for each production, and some seasons have sparse documentation.
Collection Arrangement
Materials are arranged chronologically, with the exception of Boxes 17 and 18, which contain unsorted material. Any large posters for productions are filed separately in oversize boxes.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Buildings.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.). Second Stage.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.). Theater Dept.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Theater--Connecticut--Middletown--History--20th century.; College and school drama, American--Connecticut--Middletown.
Related Material
For an in-depth study of Second Stage and this collection, see Jacqueline Chapman's honors thesis, Under Our Auspices: The Changing Identity of Wesleyan's Second Stage 1973-Present. Available in Special Collections & Archives or online at http://wesscholar.wesleyan.edu/etd_hon_theses/47/
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - Pre-Second Stage
    - Dept/'92 Theater Documents (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Spring 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1973
    - Correspondence/Notes (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Spring 1974
    - Productions (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence/Notes (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fall 1974
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Administrative (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Productions (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence + Notes (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Spring 1975
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Administrative (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Productions (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Fall 1975
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Administrative (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Productions (Box 1, Folder 18a)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Spring 1976
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Productions (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Administrative (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/Notes (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fall 1976
    - Staff/Season Notes (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Rats (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - The Man in the Bowler Hat (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - An Evening of String Chamber Music (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - The Hitchhikers (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Sweeny Agnostics (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Playing with Fire (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Lovers and other strangers / Postcards (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Feiffer's People (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - The Zoo Story (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - On Green Dolphin St. (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - The Stronger / Night / Man With a Flower in His Mouth (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - A Day in the Death of Joe Egg (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Arms and the Man (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Bertha (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - The Browning Version (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Side by Side by Side (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Show Applications (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Administration (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence/Notes (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Spring 1977
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - The Ring Cycle (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Invitation to a March (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - The Dot and the Line / Adaptation (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - The Lover (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Whispers on the Wind (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Hay Fever (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Dames at Sea (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - The Green Cockatoo (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Medea (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Endgame (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - The Gas Heart (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Show Applications (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Administrative (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 1976-1977
    - Budget and Finances (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1977
    - Staff and Season Lists (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Production Notes (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Show Applications (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Show App Responses (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Spring 1978
    - Show Applications (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Show App Responses (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1977-1978
    - Budget (Box 2, Folder 11-A)
  - Fall 1978
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 2, Folder 11-B)
    - Production Notes (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Show Applications (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Show App Responses (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Spring 1979
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Production Notes (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Show Applications (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Show App Responses (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence & Notes (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1978-1979
    - Budget/Finance (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Fall 1979
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Production Notes (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Productions (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Show Applications (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Show App Responses (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Spring 1980
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Productions (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 1979-1980
    - Budget/Finances (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1980
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Productions (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Administrative (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Spring 1981
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Productions (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1980-1981
    - Budget/Finances (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Fall 1981
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Productions (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Spring 1982
    - Staff/Season List (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Productions (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Show App response (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1981-1982
    - Budget (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fall 1982
    - Staff/Season List (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Productions (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Show Applications (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Show App Responses (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Spring 1983
    - Staff/Seasonal Lists (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 1982-1983
    - Budget (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fall 1983
    - Staff/Season (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Productions and Production Notes (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Spring 1984
    - Staff/Season (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Ionesco One Acts Jack... / Eggs (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Voices (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Portrait of a Madonna (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Agamemnon (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - The Marriage of Mr. Mississippi (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Miss Julie (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Tom Thumb (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Show Applications (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 1983-1984
    - Budget/Finances (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fall 1984-Fall 1985
    - Minutes (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1984
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Cloud Nine (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Fall Faculty Dance Concert (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Van Itallie One Acts Baglady and Sunset Freeway (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - We Won't Pay! (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Show Applications (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Administrative (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Spring 1985
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Whoreson Crawl (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Gilgamesh (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Hello Out There / After Liverpool (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Comedia dell Arte / Comedial - Oddfellows (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Man of La Moncha (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - No It's Smorgasbord / Thesis Dance Concert (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - German Play (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Absent Friends (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - And It Froze / Traps (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Saxophone Concert (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - The Stronger / Talking With... (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Untitled / Descent (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - In the Shade of the Oak / Working in Silence (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Dogg's Hamlet / Cahoot's Macbeth (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Spring Dance (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - One Sided Surfboard (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Show applications (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Administrative (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1984-1985
    - Budget, etc. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fall 1985
    - Staff and season lists (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Funeral Games (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Same Time Next Year (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Dining Room (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - True West (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Sizwe Bansi (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bremen Town Musicians/ Cinderella (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Night Must Fall (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Spot the Dots-Sterne (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - My Sister in this House (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Pajama Game-Encore (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Marie & Bruce (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Viscous Game/ Open House (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Show Applications (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Administrative (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Spring 1986
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Night of Dance (party) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Richter's Thing (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Imaginary Invalid (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - What the Butler Saw (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Coloring Grey Skies Blue (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Godspell (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Changing Paces/Thesis Dance Concert (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Fall of Silas Axe (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Cabaret-Encore! (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Spring Dance Concert (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Winning Plays (one-acts)/ Modern Miracles-Oddfellows (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Lady's Scottish Play/ The No Play (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - French Play (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Maids (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Something Unspoken/Strange Directions (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The House of Bernarda Alba (Box 5, Folder 4a)
    - The Caine Mutiny Court Martial (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The Rail (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Show Applications (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Show App Responses (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Administrative (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1985-1986
    - Budget, etc. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fall 1986
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - The Indian Wants the Bronx (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Stepshow Festival (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Distant Fires (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - La Ronde (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - The Bald Soprano (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - The Lion in Winter (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - The Telephone/Trouble in Tahiti-One Act Operas (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Krapp's Last Tape (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Mass Appeal (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - The Toilet (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Private Wars (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Show Applications (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Administrative (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1987
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Unrequited Love (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Amphigorey Stories (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Mud-McSherry (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Spring Awakening (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Alice Through the Looking Glass (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - The Actor's Nightmare (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - The Elephant Man (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Sherry (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Kaspar (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - The Sea Horse (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Spring Dance (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Show Applications (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Administrative (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - 1986-1987
    - Budget (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1987
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Good and Faithful Servant (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Interview (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Fire in the Basement (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Intro to Western Murder Mysteries (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Accidental Death of an Anarchist (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Have a Nice Weekend (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Show Applications (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Show App Responses (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Administrative (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Spring 1988
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - The Enframed (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Usonian House (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - 3x3 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Spring Dance (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - GOD (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Thesis Dance (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Judy!/ Loving the Love Goddess (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - AACT-Friends (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Death Watch (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Small Craft Warnings (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Michi's Blood (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - One Acts-Levine (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Black Comedy/ Yerma Sikkenga (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Summertree (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Open Eyes (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - ROPE (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - The Thwartings of Baron Bolligrew (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - JWD vs. The Black Holes (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Show Applications (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Show App Responses (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Staff Applications (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Administrative (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1987-1988
    - Budget and Finances (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Fall 1988
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Oxford U. Dramatic Society: As You Like It (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Zoo Story (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Danny and the Deep Blue Sea (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - The Lesson (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Waiting for Lefty (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - In Fireworks Lie Secret Codes (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Clay's Thing/ Statements after an Arrest under the Immorality Act (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Report me and my Cause/ A Right to be Unsatisfied (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Dance (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ion (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - The Real Thing (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - TV (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Deathtrap (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Persis' Thing-The Avant Garde Theater (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Show Applications (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Show App Responses (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Administrative (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Spring 1989
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - American Buffalo (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Beyond Therapy (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - The Normal Heart (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - To Ride Across Lake Constance (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Kennedy's Children (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Rosenkrantz and Guildenstern are Dead (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Crimes of the Heart (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Woza Albert! (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Light Journey (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Spring Dance (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Dumbwaiter/ Hello Out There (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - French Play (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - No Exit (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Oh Dad Poor Dad (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - The Merchants of Venice (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Dance 5/4-6 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Savage/Love (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Show Applications (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Show Applications (Not Produced/ Student Script) (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Show App Responses (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Administrative (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1988-1989
    - Budget and Finances (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - February 1989-February 1990
    - Notes (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Fall 1989
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - The Thunderstorm/ Light and Sound (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - An Evening with Samuel Becket (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - A Girl's Guide to Chaos (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Noonday Demons (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Ubu Rex (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Senior Project/ Hothouse Flowers (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Visible Rhythm's Dance Troupe: Life in Movement (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Student Playwrights (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Drinks with Shelley and Melons (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Camino Real (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - No Doz (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Show Applications (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Administrative (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - March 1990-January 1991
    - Notes (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Spring 1990
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Exit the King (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - The Public Eye (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Images of Strength (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Temptation (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - The Doctor in Spite of Himself (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Picnic (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Senior Project- the Good Mother (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - See How They Run (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - German Play (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Dusa, Fish, Stas, and Vi (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Lightning Bugs (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - FOB (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Play it Again, Sam (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - The French Play (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Francisco's Thing/ Caligula (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Spring Dance (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - High Noon Theater (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Show Applications (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Show App Responses (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Administrative (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Administrative-Picnic (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - 1989-1990
    - Budget and Finances (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Fall 1990
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Maids Firshein Project (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - The Exhibition (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Flowers for Algernon Flowers (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Colored Museum Sharp Project (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Suicide of a Dead Man ( or Echoes in a Dream or Yesterday a Man Died) / The Partridge Curse (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Agnes of God (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Opera (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Show Applications (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Administrative (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Spring 1991
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Oddfellows (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Painting Churches (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - One Person (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - I'm Dreaming, But am I? (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - As is (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Moonchildren (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Sarita (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Wait Until Dark (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Publikumsbeschimpfung German Play (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide/ When the Rainbow is Enuf (Colored Girls) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Music Major Concert (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Le Bai Des Voleurs French Play (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - And the Soul Shall Dance AACT (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Thesis Dance (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Magic Theater (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - The Winrow Works (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - A Dissolving Worm (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Expressions (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - New Plays Festival (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Show Applications (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Show App Responses (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Administrative (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 1990-1991
    - Budget and Finances (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Spring 1991-Fall 1991
    - Minutes (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Fall 1991-Fall 1992
    - Minutes (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Fall 1991
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - I Ought to be in the Pictures (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Faculty Dance (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Squirrels (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Sweeney Todd (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - The Great God Brown Dept. Theater Project (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Little Footsteps (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Show Applications (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Administrative (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Spring 1992
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Mud (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - WesRevue (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - The Children's Hour (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Le Dindon French Play (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Thesis Dance (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Paper Angels AACT (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Race on Art: An Experiment in Sharing Space Performance Piece (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - The Foreigner (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Orphans (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Spring Dance Concert (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Show Applications (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Admins (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - 1991-1992
    - Budget and Finances (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Materials removed from binder (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Additional materials (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Fall 1992
    - Button Man (Box 10, Folder 2)